[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "How did she get to the top of the business world?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "she", "get", "to", "the", "top", "of", "the", "business", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "I wanted to be a business person.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wanted", "to", "be", "a", "business", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "You know how would you sum up marriage to the Hulk?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "how", "would", "you", "sum", "up", "marriage", "to", "the", "Hulk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "You know, well, we were married for 24 years, and you know, it was great.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "well", ",", "we", "were", "married", "for", "24", "years", ",", "and", "you", "know", ",", "it", "was", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Do you feel that the relationship basically floundered the moment you heard he'd been unfaithful to you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "the", "relationship", "basically", "floundered", "the", "moment", "you", "heard", "he", "'d", "been", "unfaithful", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Why did he tell you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "he", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, in my opinion I think the reason that he had to tell me was because the woman that he was philandering with had filed a lawsuit against him, and it was probably about to be public, and I think that if he had me on his side, that they could roll it out as extortion like a lot of these celebrities do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "my", "opinion", "I", "think", "the", "reason", "that", "he", "had", "to", "tell", "me", "was", "because", "the", "woman", "that", "he", "was", "philandering", "with", "had", "filed", "a", "lawsuit", "against", "him", ",", "and", "it", "was", "probably", "about", "to", "be", "public", ",", "and", "I", "think", "that", "if", "he", "had", "me", "on", "his", "side", ",", "that", "they", "could", "roll", "it", "out", "as", "extortion", "like", "a", "lot", "of", "these", "celebrities", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "If you're honest when you'd seen other famous people get caught up in a scandal like that, and the woman stayed with the man, what was your view of women that did that before it happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "honest", "when", "you", "'d", "seen", "other", "famous", "people", "get", "caught", "up", "in", "a", "scandal", "like", "that", ",", "and", "the", "woman", "stayed", "with", "the", "man", ",", "what", "was", "your", "view", "of", "women", "that", "did", "that", "before", "it", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Before, you know, I hadn't been in that position, so I just figured that publicly they were staying with their man because of usually politicians is what you heard.", "answer_tokens": ["Before", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "had", "n't", "been", "in", "that", "position", ",", "so", "I", "just", "figured", "that", "publicly", "they", "were", "staying", "with", "their", "man", "because", "of", "usually", "politicians", "is", "what", "you", "heard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Have you'd gone through that thought in your head and thought, I would leave him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "'d", "gone", "through", "that", "thought", "in", "your", "head", "and", "thought", ",", "I", "would", "leave", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "How many other women do you think there probably were?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "other", "women", "do", "you", "think", "there", "probably", "were", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "You know, just a rough guess I think there might have been three or four, but, you know, that's just my guess.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "just", "a", "rough", "guess", "I", "think", "there", "might", "have", "been", "three", "or", "four", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "just", "my", "guess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Did you have days when you wish you were still with him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "days", "when", "you", "wish", "you", "were", "still", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Does he regret it, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "regret", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "I think he does.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Has he tried to win you back?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "tried", "to", "win", "you", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "You know, because we were going through so much stuff with the divorce and then, of course, my son had that tragic accident, and there was just a lot on our plate to sort out, and I think that he had already moved on to a new girlfriend by the time I had filed for divorce.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "because", "we", "were", "going", "through", "so", "much", "stuff", "with", "the", "divorce", "and", "then", ",", "of", "course", ",", "my", "son", "had", "that", "tragic", "accident", ",", "and", "there", "was", "just", "a", "lot", "on", "our", "plate", "to", "sort", "out", ",", "and", "I", "think", "that", "he", "had", "already", "moved", "on", "to", "a", "new", "girlfriend", "by", "the", "time", "I", "had", "filed", "for", "divorce", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "And is it 10 times worse when it has to be conducted in the public eye because you're with a famous guy?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "10", "times", "worse", "when", "it", "has", "to", "be", "conducted", "in", "the", "public", "eye", "because", "you", "'re", "with", "a", "famous", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "There aren't many of him to the (INAUDIBLE), are there?", "question_tokens": ["There", "are", "n't", "many", "of", "him", "to", "the", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "are", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "It was phenomenal being married to him.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "phenomenal", "being", "married", "to", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Terry", "Nick"]}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Do you blame Terry for the fact that he took the car out?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "blame", "Terry", "for", "the", "fact", "that", "he", "took", "the", "car", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "You know, I'm sure Terry trusted Nick, but he should have maybe thought a little bit more about the conditions, the fact that the boys were jet skiing all day and they were out in the hot sun.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "Terry", "trusted", "Nick", ",", "but", "he", "should", "have", "maybe", "thought", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "about", "the", "conditions", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "boys", "were", "jet", "skiing", "all", "day", "and", "they", "were", "out", "in", "the", "hot", "sun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Terry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "How did you deal with that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "deal", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "It was actually shocking.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "actually", "shocking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "John, I believe, is now out of the hospital and he's home.", "answer_tokens": ["John", ",", "I", "believe", ",", "is", "now", "out", "of", "the", "hospital", "and", "he", "'s", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Do you have any contact with his family?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "contact", "with", "his", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, that was a blow.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "was", "a", "blow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "She talks all about how she's sorry and that this love affair they had couldn't be denied, blah, blah, blah, and I was like, are you kidding me?", "question_tokens": ["She", "talks", "all", "about", "how", "she", "'s", "sorry", "and", "that", "this", "love", "affair", "they", "had", "could", "n't", "be", "denied", ",", "blah", ",", "blah", ",", "blah", ",", "and", "I", "was", "like", ",", "are", "you", "kidding", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "That was like a final kick in the teeth for you.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "like", "a", "final", "kick", "in", "the", "teeth", "for", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "You know, living with the enemy, you know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "living", "with", "the", "enemy", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "I bet part of you was thinking exactly that, checkmate, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "bet", "part", "of", "you", "was", "thinking", "exactly", "that", ",", "checkmate", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "I mean he's like a young Hulk, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "he", "'s", "like", "a", "young", "Hulk", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Yeah, he is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "he", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "How does Terry deal with Charlie?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "Terry", "deal", "with", "Charlie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "He doesn't really like the idea.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "really", "like", "the", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Terry", "Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "When you know what you want to do, do something?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "know", "what", "you", "want", "to", "do", ",", "do", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Well, it's go for yours.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "go", "for", "yours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Pretty embarrassing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Pretty", "embarrassing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "I don't think so because --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "because", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Do you ever have that feeling?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "have", "that", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "I just love how much my husband loves my daughter.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "love", "how", "much", "my", "husband", "loves", "my", "daughter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "Once you're a businesswoman and you've got the cover of \"Forbes Magazine,\" then what do you do?", "question_tokens": ["Once", "you", "'re", "a", "businesswoman", "and", "you", "'ve", "got", "the", "cover", "of", "``", "Forbes", "Magazine", ",", "''", "then", "what", "do", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNPS", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "You give back.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "give", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]